m1net.com.sg 2012-02-19

# M1Net Ltd

**I.** We will be responsible for all personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) collected on our website. All Personal Data collected will only be used and processed fairly and in accordance with applicable local legislation while in our possession or custody. Please be assured that we are accountable for our organisation's compliance to this Privacy Policy Code (the “Code”). 

**II.** Should there be any request or requirement by any government or authorised entity for Personal Data to be released to a third party (other than you, the M1 Group of Companies or its employees), we will take reasonable steps to ensure that such Personal Data will be processed and released strictly in accordance with applicable local legislation and this Code. 

**III.** The identity of the person(s) designated by our organisation to oversee compliance with applicable local legislation and this Code shall be made known upon request. 

**I.** We collect Personal Data for the purpose of user registration and other transactional purposes on our website: 

  * We use your IP address to help increase efficiency, diagnose possible problems with our servers, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.
  * Our online surveys, contests and competitions may also request visitors/customers for contact information. Contact information (e.g. email addresses) are collected.
  * Information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners may be sent to our customers. Contact information may also be used to get in touch with customers where necessary.
  * You may opt-out of receiving future mailings – please see the choice/opt-out section below.

**II.** We are the sole owner of all Personal Data collected on this website. 

**I.** All Personal Data collected will strictly be used or disclosed for the specified and legitimate purposes for which it was collected only. We do not use Personal Data for any other purposes unless we have obtained specific consent from users. 

**II.** Users may withdraw consent for the use of their Personal Data at any time, subject to legal or regulatory or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. Users may only be subjected to consequences because of this decision where the information is required to fulfill the specified and legitimate purposes set out by the organisation. 

**I.** Save for Personal Data described in this Code, we will not collect any other sensitive information from users. 

**II.** We limit both the amount and type of Personal Data collected to that which is necessary for the specified purpose. Please be assured that as far as possible, only necessary Personal Data will be collected from our registered users and for business purposes only. 

**I.** We will not disclose, share, transfer, sell or rent Personal Data to any third parties save for government or regulatory bodies. We do not send unsolicited marketing emails to our users. While registered users may occasionally receive emails on special promotions, out of respect for the privacy of our users, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line of such emails. 

**II.** We do not keep Personal Data for longer than is necessary for the purposes for which Personal Data are collected. Should the use of Personal Data be required for another purpose, user’s approval will be obtained prior to such use. 

**III.** We have developed guidelines and implemented procedures to govern the destruction of Personal Data that are no longer required. 

**IV.** We do not use "cookies", “web-bugs” or any other tracking technologies to collect information from users of our website. 

**V.** We will not display or make publicly available, whether through online directories, customer lists or otherwise, any Personal Data that is collected. 

**VI.** All Personal Data are kept in confidence and in accordance with applicable legislation. 

All collected Personal Data are accurate as at the time they are received from the users and will not be tampered with. 

**I.** We ensure all users that appropriate security measures are in place to protect Personal Data against unauthorised access, misuse, disclosure, copying, use, alteration, accidental loss or theft, destruction or damage. 

**II.** Only authorised personnel have access to our systems. 

**III.** All employees in our organisation are aware of the importance of maintaining confidentiality of Personal Data collected from users. Circulars are distributed to all employees to ensure they are aware of such compliance. 

**I.** This Code is displayed on our website and it is set out in the same language medium (English). We encourage all users to read this Code so as to better understand our objectives in collecting your Personal Data. 

**II.** Users may write to us to request or to obtain details of the Personal Data collected by our organisation. 

**III.** All feedback and requests can be made to the following email contact:  [wirelesssg@m1.com.sg](mailto:wirelesssg@m1.com.sg). 

Visitors are given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where information is requested of visitors. 

**I.** We allow users the right to access their Personal Data. Users may access their Personal Data by logging in using their respective username and password. 

**II.** If you would like to update your Personal Data or if you no longer wish to share your Personal Data, you may correct, update or remove your Personal Data at the member information page or email our Customer Support. 

**III.** We will respond to all feedback and requests within a reasonable time. 

We welcome all feedback or inquiries about our policies and procedures relating to Personal Data. Please be assured that we will take appropriate measures to amend our policies and procedures our policies and procedures are found to be insufficient or wanting. 

Children (users under the age of 18 years) are required to obtain consent from their parents and/or legal guardian(s) prior to registering for any service on our website. By their continued usage of the website, they are deemed to have obtained the requisite consent and consent to our collection and use of their Personal Data. 

This website contains links to other sites. M1 Net cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This Code applies solely to Personal Data collected by this website. 

If you have any questions about this Code, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact the M1Net Webmaster at   [wirelesssg@m1.com.sg](mailto:wirelesssg@m1.com.sg).
